import 'package:test_application/features/quiz/data/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is the capital of France?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Madrid',
      'B Paris',
      'C Berlin',
      'D Rome',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. In what continent is Brazil located?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Europe',
      'B Asia',
      'C North America',
      'D South America',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Earth',
      'B Jupiter',
      'C Saturn',
      'D Venus',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. What is the longest river in the world?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'A Nile',
      'B Amazon',
      'C Mississippi',
      'D Danube',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. Who is the main character in the Harry Potter series?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'A Hermione Granger',
      'B Ron Weasley',
      'C Harry Potter',
      'D Neville Longbottom',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. What is the smallest planet in our solar system?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Venus',
      'B Mars',
      'C Earth',
      'D Mercury',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. Who wrote the play Romeo and Juliet?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'A William Shakespeare',
      'B Oscar Wilde',
      'C Jane Austen',
      'D Charles Dickens',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. What is the highest mountain in the world?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Mont Blanc',
      'B Everest',
      'C Kilimanjaro',
      'D Aconcagua',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '9. What is the name of the famous painting by Leonardo da Vinci that depicts a woman?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Starry Night',
      'B The Persistence of Memory',
      'C The Last Supper',
      'D Mona Lisa',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. What is the capital of France?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Madrid',
      'B Paris',
      'C Berlin',
      'D Rome',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '11. In what continent is Brazil located?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Europe',
      'B Asia',
      'C North America',
      'D South America',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '12. What is the largest planet in our solar system?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Earth',
      'B Jupiter',
      'C Saturn',
      'D Venus',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '13. What is the longest river in the world?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'A Nile',
      'B Amazon',
      'C Mississippi',
      'D Danube',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '14. Who is the main character in the Harry Potter series?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'A Hermione Granger',
      'B Ron Weasley',
      'C Harry Potter',
      'D Neville Longbottom',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '15. What is the smallest planet in our solar system?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Venus',
      'B Mars',
      'C Earth',
      'D Mercury',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '16. Who wrote the play Romeo and Juliet?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'A William Shakespeare',
      'B Oscar Wilde',
      'C Jane Austen',
      'D Charles Dickens',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '17. What is the highest mountain in the world?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Mont Blanc',
      'B Everest',
      'C Kilimanjaro',
      'D Aconcagua',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    '18. What is the name of the famous painting by Leonardo da Vinci that depicts a woman?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Starry Night',
      'B The Persistence of Memory',
      'C The Last Supper',
      'D Mona Lisa',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '19. What is the highest mountain in the world?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'A Mont Blanc',
      'B Everest',
      'C Kilimanjaro',
      'D Aconcagua',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
    '20. What is the name of the famous painting by Leonardo da Vinci that depicts a woman?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'A Starry Night',
      'B The Persistence of Memory',
      'C The Last Supper',
      'D Mona Lisa',
    ],
  ),
];
